setf.com 2019-02-04

# FACTS

                                                                                                                    Rev. 01/18
                      WHAT DOES WORLD OMNI FINANCIAL CORP. (FOR ITSELF AND DOING BUSINESS
 FACTS                AS SOUTHEAST TOYOTA FINANCE) DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
 Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                      consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                      how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                      understand what we do.
 What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                      have with us. This information can include:
                            Social Security number and account balances
                            Payment history and transaction or loss history
                            Credit history and credit scores
 How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                      business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’
                      personal information; the reasons World Omni Financial Corp./Southeast Toyota Finance chooses
                      to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
  Reasons we can share your personal information             Does World Omni/Southeast Can you limit this sharing?
                                                                Toyota Finance share?
For our everyday business purposes –
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                         Yes                            No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes –
to offer our products and services to you                                  Yes                            No
For joint marketing with other financial companies                         Yes                            No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your transactions and experiences                        Yes                            No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
information about your creditworthiness                                    Yes                           Yes
For our affiliates to market to you                                        Yes                           Yes
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                         Yes                           Yes
To limit              Call 1-800-553-0159 – our menu will prompt you through your choice(s)
our sharing           Please note:
                      If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent
                      this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                      described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us at any time to limit our sharing.
Questions?            Call 1-800-329-0746
                                                                                                                    C/S# 4306

   Page 2
   What we do
   How does World Omni/Southeast                    To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and
   Toyota Finance protect my                        use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These
   personal information?                            measures include computer safeguards and secured files and
                                                    buildings.
   How does World Omni/Southeast                    We collect your personal information, for example, when you
   Toyota Finance collect my personal
   information?                                          Apply for financing or apply for a lease
                                                         Provide account information or pay us by check
                                                         Give us your contact information
                                                    We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                                    bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
   Why can’t I limit all sharing?                   Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                                         sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes –
                                                         information about your creditworthiness
                                                         affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                                         sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                                    State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                                    limit sharing. See below for more on your rights under state law.
   What happens when I limit sharing                Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
   for an account I hold jointly with
   someone else?
   Definitions
   Affiliates                                       Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                    financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                         Our affiliates include financial companies such as CenterOne
                                                         Financial Services LLC, and nonfinancial companies such as
                                                         DataScan Holdings LLC and its subsidiaries, Jim Moran &
                                                         Associates, Inc., JM Family Enterprises, Inc., and Southeast
                                                         Toyota Distributors, LLC and its subsidiaries.
   Nonaffiliates                                    Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                                    financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                                         Nonaffiliates we share with can include motor vehicle dealers in
                                                         Alabama, Florida, Georgia, North Carolina and South Carolina.
   Joint marketing                                  A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                                    together market financial products or services to you.
                                                         Our joint marketing partners include consumer finance companies.
   Other important information
   California Residents:
   Unless you have given your express written consent, we will not share your personal information for our affiliates
   to market to you or for other non-marketing purposes, for nonaffiliates to market to you, or for joint marketing with
   other financial companies.
   Vermont Residents:
   We will not disclose information about your credit worthiness to our affiliates and will not disclose your personal
   information, financial information, credit report, or health information to non-affiliated third parties to market to you,
   other than as permitted by Vermont law, unless you authorize us to make those disclosures. Additional information
   concerning our privacy polices can be found by calling 1-800-329-0746.
Texas Residents:
For questions or complaints about your contract with us, contact World Omni/Southeast Toyota Finance at 1-800-329-
0746. World Omni/Southeast Toyota Finance is licensed and examined under Texas law by the Office of Consumer
Credit Commissioner (OCCC), a state agency. If a complaint or question cannot be resolved by contacting World Omni/
Southeast Toyota Finance, consumers can contact the OCCC to file a complaint or ask a general credit related question.
OCCC address: 2601 N. Lamar Blvd., Austin, Texas 78705. Phone: (800) 538-1579. Fax: (512) 936-7610. Website: occc.
texas.gov. Email: consumer.complaints@occc.texas.gov.
